지난 이야기
Previously on Friends....
마르셀을 찾았어
여기 뉴욕에서 영화를 찍는대
I tracked down Marcel. And get this:
He's here in New York filming
Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
'아웃브레이크 II
바이러스의 맨해튼 침공'
어이, 친구
마르셀!
Hey, buddy! Marcel!
죄송하지만 여긴...
Excuse me, this is a
Closed set. We know.
But we're friends with the monkey.
비공개 세트장이라구요?
우린 원숭이 친구들이에요
안녕, 누구를 데려왔게?
네 친구 해리 엘라폰테!
Good morning.
Look who I brought!
Your old friend, Harry Elafonte!
이런...
Whoa, dude. Burn!
I don't get it.
왜 저럴까?
어제 날 보고는 좋아했는데
He seemed so happy
to see me yesterday.
피곤해서 그러니 상심 말아요
뜨면 다들 저렇죠 뭐
Don't take it personal. He's under
pressure, starring in a movie and all.
How big of a star is Marcel?
마르셀이 얼마나 인기 있죠?
사람하고 비교하면요?
In human terms? I'd say...
시빌 세퍼드 정도?
... Cybill Shepherd.
So you guys in the movie
or you just really paranoid?
영화배우들인가요?
아님 광적인 영화팬들?
이봐요
Hey, Sal?
Jerry wants to know
if the monkey's ready.
지하철 신에 원숭이 준비되는지
제리가 물어 보래요
Excuse me?
'제리'가 감독님이신가요?
Jerry is the director?
Which one's he?
어디 계시죠?
-The one in the director's chair?
-Gotcha.
감독님 의자에 앉아 계시죠
알았어요
피비, 나랑 좀 걷자
Pheebs, walk with me.
좋아, 그런데 왜
걸어야 하는데?
Why am I walking with you?
We're just going over here
so that we can get away from...
여기서 탈출하려고 그러지
끔찍한 바이러스로부터!
...the horrible flesh-eating virus!
아가씨, 내 말 명심해!
For the love of God, woman,
listen to me!
Is he looking? Is he looking?
감독님이 보시니?
The One With the Super Bowl, Part 2
-We've got a problem.
-Tell me.
- 일이 생겼어
- 안녕, 뭔데?
크리스의 화장을 못해주겠어
있는 콧수염을 없다고 우기잖아
I can't do Chris' makeup.
She refuses to acknowledge
her mustache.
- 보기 흉해?
- 눈썹이 코에 붙은 것 같아
-ls it bad?
-lt looks like her eyebrow fell down.
Unless we convince her
to let me bleach it...
당장 표백시키지 않으면
...Van Damme will be
making out with Gabe Kaplan.
장 클로드 반담은
상대역이 원시인인 줄 알걸
I'll talk to her.
내가 말해 볼게
I hate actors.
배우가 싫어
Nice camouflage. For a minute there,
I almost didn't see you.
위장술이 멋지네요
있는지도 몰랐어요
Excuse me.
실례해요
이름이 챈들러 아니에요?
Is your name Chandler?
그런데요?
Yes, it is.
Chandler Bing.
챈들러 빙 맞지?
Do you know me or are you
just really good at this game?
날 알아요? 아님 원래
이름 맞히기 선수예요?
I'm Susie Moss.
나 수지 모스야
Fourth grade? Glasses?
초등학교 4학년, '안경'
I carried a box of
animal crackers like a purse?
크래커 상자를 늘
지갑처럼 들고 다니던 애
Susie Moss!
수지 모스! 맞아
Right! Yeah! Wow!
You look....
너 완전히 용됐다
Great job growing up.
It's nice to see you don't still
wear the cap with the mirrors on it.
넌 거울 붙인 모자 안 쓰니까
사람 돼 보인다
4학년 끝난 이후로
중매쟁이 짓은 청산했어
I graduated fourth grade
and realized I wasn't a pimp.
Remember the class play?
학예회 때 기억나?
네가 내 치마를 걷어올려서
내 속옷 패션쇼 됐던 거
You pulled up my skirt and the
entire auditorium saw my underpants?
Yes. Back then, I used humor
as a defense mechanism.
그 땐 유머가 내 무기였지
Thank God I don't do that anymore.
이젠 그런 짓 안 해
-Oh, my God!
-What? What?
- 세상에! 어떡해!
- 왜 그래?
It's Jean-Claude Van Damme.
장 클로드 반담이야
I didn't know he was in
this movie. He is so hot!
이 영화에 나오는 줄 몰랐어
너무 멋지다!
You think?
저 남자가?
The Muscles from Brussels?
Wham-Bam-Van-Damme?
'브뤼셀의 근육질'
'끝내주는 반담' 몰라?
Did you see Time Cop?
'타임캅'도 안 봤어?
안 봤어, 거기서 멋있었니?
No. Was he any good in it?
타임이고 뭐고 뻑 같다니까
Rachel, he totally changed time!
So why don't you go talk to him?
- 그럼 가서 말 걸어 봐
- 안 돼
왜? 가서 멋있다고 말하면
어떻게 되는데?
Go tell him he's cute.
What's the worst that could happen?
He could hear me.
듣긴 하겠지
-I'm doing it for you.
-Don't you dare! Don't!
- 내가 대신 말해 줄게
- 안 돼, 하지 마
Don't!
안 된다니까!
Tell him I cook!
요리사라고 말해
Excuse me.
- 실례합니다, 안녕하세요?
- 안녕
좀 바보 같은 소리지만...
This is gonna sound kind of goofy...
저기 있는 제 친구가...
... but my friend over there...
...who cooks, by the way....
요리사인데요
당신이 멋있대요
She thinks you're cute.
You don't think I'm cute?
당신은 나 안 멋있어?
I don't know.
글쎄요
본인이 멋있다고 생각해요?
Do you think you're cute?
We're getting off the track.
I was supposed to tell you...
좋아요, 난 친구 대신
댁이 멋있다고 말하러 왔으니
... my friend thinks you're cute.
친구한테 뭐라고 할까요?
What should I tell her?
You can tell her
I think her friend is cute.
가서 당신 친구의 친구가
귀엽더라고 말해 줘
- 분장!
- 나야, 가야겠어
-Makeup!
-That's me. I gotta go.
그래
네 팔을 얼마나 더 만져야
나한테 데이트 신청할 거야?
How many times must I touch you on
the arm before you ask me on a date?
Well, let's try one more.
한 번만 더 만져 봐
There you go. Ernie's, 8:00?
어니스에서 8시에 봐
I'll be there.
갈게, 잘되면 이번엔 내가
네 속옷을 볼지도 모르겠네
And if things go well,
maybe this time...
... I'll get to see your underwear.
No one was around to hear that?
누구 같이 들은 사람 없수?
So what'd he say?
뭐라든?
별꼴이야, 왜 네 얘기를
전하는 나한테 추근대지?
What a jerk!
I kept talking about you,
and he kept asking me out.
Naturally, you know, I said no.
당연히 난 안 된다고 했지
어쨌든 고마워
Thanks, anyway.
He just kept asking...
그런데 자꾸, 자꾸, 자꾸...
묻는 거야
...and asking, asking, asking....
If you want to go out
with him, you can.
네가 만나고 싶으면 만나
좀 황당하긴 하지만
괜찮아...
Sounds like a jerk to me, but
Jean-Claude, she said yes!
I'll see you tonight!
장 클로드, 얘가 괜찮대요!
저녁에 만나요!
Thank you.
고마워
Then Jean-Claude took me
to Crossroads...
장 클로드가 데려간 곳에서
드류 베리모어와 합세했어
...and we hung out
with Drew Barrymore.
드류는 정말 끝내주지
그 풍만한 가슴하며...
Oh, man. She's so smokin'!
She's got the greatest set of
No guys around, huh?
남자가 없네
뭐 필요한 거 없어?
-Does anybody need anything?
-I'll have an espresso.
에스프레소 한 잔 줘
아냐, 내가 가져올게
I'll get it.
If I ask you to, you'll end up
drinking it yourself.
괜히 부탁했다가 그것마저
네가 마셔 버리면 어떡해?
말도 안 돼
-That is so unfair.
-I know.
그래, 반담 때문에 배신하고
커피까지 마시면 말도 안 되지
Like you'd drink her coffee after
what you did to her with Van Damme?
I have to cancel racquetball tonight.
조이, 오늘 밤 라켓볼 약속은
취소해야겠다
Marcel's trainer will let me
have him for a couple of hours.
조련사가 2시간 동안
마르셀을 빌려 준대
You're blowing me off for a monkey?
원숭이 때문에 날 바람맞혀?
토요일에 쳐도 되잖아
We can reschedule for Saturday.
비둘기랑 약속 안 꼬이면
Unless you hook up
with a bunch of pigeons.
나 한번 찔러 봐
완전히 구워삶아졌어
Stick a fork in me...
... I am done!
찔러 보다니?
Stick a fork what?
Like when you're cooking a steak.
고기가 익으면 그러잖아
난 채식주의자야
I don't eat meat.
How do you know vegetables are done?
야채 익은 건 어떻게 알지?
Well, you don't.
You eat them and you can tell.
그냥 먹어 보면 알아
그럼 날 먹어 봐, 익었어
Okay, then eat me, I'm done!
I've met the perfect woman.
- 완벽한 여자를 만났어
- 정말?
We're sitting on her couch,
fooling around...
그녀의 소파에서 장난치는데
문득 날 보더니 이러지 뭐야
...and then she turns to me and says:
"Did you ever want to do it
in an elevator?"
'엘리베이터에서
해보고 싶었어?'
What did you say?
- 넌 뭐랬는데?
- 확실히 이랬지
I believe my exact words were....
버벅버벅...
내가 거기서 하고 싶을지
어떻게 알겠어?
How do you know if you wanna do that?
닥치면 알게 돼
You just know.
We gotta go.
Got a reservation in 30 minutes.
가야지!
30분 후에 예약해 놨잖아
아니, 안 돼
What I had planned shouldn't take
more than two, three minutes, tops.
내가 하려는 건 기껏해야
2, 3분밖에 안 걸려
200초 간의 열정이라
Two hundred seconds of passion!
We gotta go.
가야 돼!
좋은 생각이 있어
But...
... here's an idea.
너 여자 팬티 입어 봤어?
Have you ever worn women's underwear?
Well, yes, actually...
솔직히 입어 봤는데...
... but they were my Aunt Edna's.
숙모 거였지
And there were three of us in there.
사람 셋은 들어가겠더라
I was thinking
it would be kind of sexy...
오늘 밤 저녁식사 때 네가
내 걸 입으면 정말 섹시할 거야
...if you wore mine tonight
at dinner.
네 팬티를 나보고 입으라고?
You want me to wear your panties?
Could you?
할 수 있어?
If I was wearing your underwear...
내가 네 팬티를 입으면
넌 뭘 입을 건데?
...then what would you be wearing?
You're swell!
너 흥분했구나
마르셀이 제일 좋아하는
바나나 케이크를 만들었어
I made Marcel's favorite dish,
banana cake...
...with mealworm.
쌀벌레도 넣고
Candle.
촛불씩이나!
What do you think's
gonna happen here tonight?
오늘 밤 일 내는 거 아냐?
여보세요?
안녕하세요, 오는 중인가요?
Hi, are you on your way over
No, I understand.
A monkey's gotta work.
아뇨, 이해해요
원숭이도 일을 해야죠
아뇨, 괜찮아요
저도 다른 볼일이 있어요
It's no big deal.
It's not like I had
anything special planned.
네, 그래요
괜찮아요, 안녕히 계세요
Rachel, why don't you
start talking first?
레이첼, 먼저 말해 봐
난 정말 말도 안 된다고 봐
쟤가 괜찮다고 해서...
I feel that this is
totally unjustified.
She gave me the green light,
I did nothing
Do you think I can't
see you in the TV set?
TV 화면에 안 비치는 줄 알아?
If there's something
you'd like to share
좋아, 모니카
너도 할말 있으면 해봐
인간의 탈을 쓰고 어떻게 그래?
You had no right to date him!
-That's the most ridiculous
-You sold me out!
무슨 말을 그렇게 해?
- 넌 날 팔았어!
- 웃기지 마!
-I did not!
-You absolutely
- 명백히 판 거야
- 나도 말 좀 하자
Would you let me talk!
Did you just flick me?
지금 나 쳤어?
Well, you wouldn't let me
finish and I was
말도 안 끝났는데
중간에 자르니까...
That hurt!
아파!
Quit flicking!
꽤 치는데!
Stop flicking!
- 그만 쳐!
- 네가 시작했잖아
You flicked me first!
이러지들 마
그만 좀 해
Let's not do this!
좋게 해결해, 좋게!
Happy thoughts!
둘 다 나한테 혼나 볼래?
Now I'm gonna kick some ass!
그만 싸운다면 놔줄게
All right. Now, I will
let go if you both stop.
그를 만나지 말라는 거야?
You want me to stop seeing him?
그래
그저 네가 만나고 싶어한다는
말만 해주란 거지?
You want me to just tell him
you're seeing him instead?
Is that what you want?
맞아
That's what you want?
- 그걸 바란다고?
- 그래
-Fine!
- 좋아
됐어
There we go.
If we were in prison,
you guys would be, like, my bitches.
감옥이었으면 너희는
내 똘마니 감이야
- 나도 끼워 줘서 고마워
- 그런 말 마
Thanks for letting me tag along.
Forget about it.
How you doing there, squirmy?
그건 어때?
간신히 버티고 있어
I'm hanging in.
And a little out.
조금 삐져 나왔어
So assistant to the director?
조감독이시라죠?
That's an exciting job. You must
have a ton of responsibilities
정말 재밌겠네요
이것저것 책임이 많으시죠?
- 배우 캐스팅 권한은 없어요
- 뭐 먹을래?
I don't do the casting.
So what are you guys gonna eat?
How come all I can think about is
putting that ice in my mouth...
네가 내 입에 저 얼음을 넣고
녹여 주면 얼마나 좋을까?
...and licking you all over?
Because I went to an all-boys high
school, and God is making up for it?
남자고등학교를 다녔다고
하느님이 상을 내리시는구나
I want you right here...
난 바로 이 자리에서
당장 하고 싶어
... right now.
Right now, right here?
여기서, 당장?
Don't you think we're in
kind of a public place?
너무 공공장소 아닐까?
저쪽은 새우를 먹겠다네
They do have the shrimp.
Meet me in the bathroom.
화장실에서 봐
나 화장실 갔다 올게!
I'm going to the bathroom now.
Come on.
들어와
All right, mister.
어디 팬티 좀 볼까?
Let's see those panties.
알았어
Alrighty.
어떻게 하면 더 섹시하게?
But you know what
would be even sexier?
뭐지?
What?
셔츠를 팬티 안에
넣어 입지 마
If you didn't have
your shirt tucked into them.
팬티만 입은 걸 보고 싶어
다른 건 다 벗어 버려
All right. Now, I would like
to see you wearing nothing but them.
Take your clothes off.
이러는 동안 특별요리를
놓친다는 거 알아둬
I hope you realize this means
we'll miss hearing about the specials.
Come on, hurry!
얼른 벗어!
Do you want this done quick
or done right?
빨리 벗을까?
아님 섹시하게 벗을까?
돌아 봐
뒷모습을 보고 싶어
All right, turn around.
I wanna see you from behind.
'강철 같은 엉덩이'
비디오를 보는 것 같은데
Somebody's been doing
his Buns of Steel video.
엉덩이 조이기도 할까?
So you want me
to clench anything or...?
수지?
Susie?
수지!
이건 4학년 때의 복수다
This is for the fourth grade.
- 무슨 소리야?
- 무슨 소리냐구?
-What do you mean?
-What do I mean?
무슨 소리인지 몰라서 물어?
팬티가 내 대답이다, 어쩔래?
What do I mean?!
I mean underpants, mister!
That's what I mean!
What? What do you mean?
그게 무슨 말이야?
My skirt...
네가 내 치마를 들어올려서
애들이 다 웃었어
...you lifted. IKids laughing!
그 바람에 18살까지 별명이
'빤스'였다구!
I was Susie Underpants till I was 18!
That was in fourth grade!
How could you still be upset?
겨우 4학년 때 일이야
여태 그걸로 화를 내?
20년 후에 나한테 와서
'나 아직도 화났어' 하지 마
Call me in 20 years and tell me
if you're still upset about this.
I hope you realize you're not
getting these underpants back!
이러면 네 팬티
못 찾는다는 걸 알아야지!
믿어지지가 않네요
I can't believe this.
Just two weeks ago,
I was watching Sudden Death...
2주 전만 해도 영화에서 봤는데
이렇게 데이트를 하다니
...and now I'm on a date
with Jean-Claude Van Damme.
Can you beat up that guy?
저 남자 이길 수 있어요?
- 저 남자도 이길 수 있어요?
- 그럼
-Can you beat up that guy?
-Sure.
정말 멋져요
This is so wild.
몰래 데이트에 응해 줄지
상상도 못했어요
I gotta admit, I was surprised
that you agreed to go on a blind date.
보통 때는 안 해
Normally, I would not do it.
What made you make
the exception for me?
그럼 왜 나만 특별히 해주죠?
레이첼 말이 나랑 드류 베리모어
이렇게 셋이서 자길 원한다길래
Rachel told me...
...you were dying to have a threesome
with me and Drew Barrymore.
By the way, Drew has
some ground rules and....
하지만 드류도
지킬 건 지킨다고
- 어서 사과해
- 싫어
Say you're sorry!
Say it!
- 사과해
- 싫어, 내가 왜 사과해?
No! I'm not gonna!
사과해!
Say it! Say it!
Great!
좋아, 레이첼
Say you're sorry
or your sweater gets it.
사과할래?
아니면 네 스웨터 망칠까?
내가 제일 아끼는 거야
세 번째 데이트 때 입는 거라구
That is my favorite sweater!
That is my third-date sweater!
Say you're sorry.
미안하다고 말해
한번 해보자는 거야?
You wanna play?
Okay, let's play.
좋아, 어디 해보자
Let's play.
뭐야?
What'll you do?
스웨터 안 돌려주면
핸드백이 소스로 떡칠될걸
Give me back my sweater
or it's handbag marinara.
You don't have the guts.
그럴 용기도 없으면서
Yeah? At least I wasn't too chicken
to tell some guy he was cute.
난 최소한 좋아하는 남자한테
말도 못 거는 촌닭은 아냐
됐어!
이 광란을 중단해!
Stop! Stop the madness!
This is crazy!
미쳤구나
Who can remember why
you're fighting in the first place?
뭐 때문에 싸웠는지
기억이나 나니?
Yes, that's right.
그래, 맞아
But still....
그렇지만 네 가방 좀 봐
Look at your purse!
Look at your sweater!
넌 네 스웨터를 봐
너희 자신들을 봐
Look at yourselves!
스웨터 수선해 줄게
I'll help you fix your sweater.
I'll help you...
핸드백... 버려 줄게
...throw out your purse.
I'm sorry I made you stop seeing him.
그 사람 못 만나게 해서
미안해
I'm sorry I went out with him
when I knew you liked him.
네가 좋아하는 거 알면서
만나서 미안해
I'm sorry that I borrowed your gloves.
네 장갑 빌려서 미안해
Joey?
- 조이?
- 엄마?
Ma?
- 조이!
- 챈들러?
What are you doing here?
I thought you guys took off.
여태 여기 있어?
둘이 내뺐을 줄 알았는데
걔 혼자 내뺐어
내 옷까지 챙겨서!
She took off with my clothes!
- 지금 홀랑 벗고 있어?
- 완전히는 아냐
-Are you naked in there?
-Well, not exactly.
여자 팬티는 걸쳤어
I'm wearing panties.
항상 그러고 다녔니?
You always wear panties?
아니, 이번이 처음이야
No, no. This is the first time.
재수 더럽게 없구나
Talk about your bad luck!
The first time you try panties and
someone walks off with your clothes.
여자 속옷 처음 입은 날
홀랑 벗겨지다니
누가 입고 싶어서 입었냐?
수지가 시켰다구
I was not trying them out.
Susie asked me to wear them.
- 어디 보자
- 안 돼!
Let me see!
No! I'm not letting you
or anybody else see, ever!
너는 물론이고
아무도 보면 안 돼!
알았어
All right, all right!
실오라기만 달랑 걸쳤네
Someone's flossing!
조이, 그런 거
싫어하는 사람도 있어
Joey, some people don't like that.
Chandler's wearing panties.
- 챈들러가 여자 팬티 입었어
- 뭐?
What?
-Let me see!
-You don't have to see!
- 나도 보자
- 안 돼, 보지 마
Hi, tushy!
궁둥이 예쁜데
- 얼른 속옷 벗어 줘
- 안 돼, 싫어!
One of you give me your underpants.
I'm not wearing any.
난 안 입어서 안 돼
How can you not be wearing any?
어떻게 속옷을 안 입냐?
I'm getting heat from the guy
in the hot pink thong.
분홍색 끈만 두른 놈이
그러니까 열받네
로스, 네 팬티 50달러에 살게
Look, Ross. I'll give you
$50 for your underpants.
안녕하세요?
피비, 우유 좀 남겨 줘
-Can I have the milk?
-I'm almost done with it.
벌써 다 넣었어
넌 여자 팬티나 챙겨
Keep your panties on.
얘들아, 나 영화에 출연한다
And I'm in the movie!
정말?
-What happened?
-A virus victim called in sick...
바이러스 희생자 한 명이 아프대
캐티가 추천해 줘서 됐어
...so Cathy recommended me and boom!
I'm dying on a gurney!
들것에 실려 나가는 환자 역이야
잘됐다
로스, 마르셀의 마지막 촬영이
끝났는데 가서 작별인사 해
Marcel just finished his last scene,
if you wanna go say goodbye.
됐어, 다른 스태프들하고
파티하겠지 뭐
That's okay. He's probably
got parties to go to and stuff.
한 곳에 매어 있는
체질이 아니니 내버려둬야지
He's moved on.
That's the way it goes, right?
- 세상에!
- 왜?
Oh, my God!
What?
Looks like we made it
Left each other on the way...
... to another love
Looks like we made it
Or I thought so, till today
Until you were there, everywhere
And all I could taste was
Love the way we made it
Looks like we made it
이 모든 것을 노래하고 싶어
I think I want to write
a song about all this.
그래?
기타줄 하나 끊어진 건 빼고
Except one of the strings
on my guitar is broken.
Chandler, can I borrow your G-string?
챈들러, 줄 하나만 빌려 줄래?
-How long you been waiting to say that?
-About 20 minutes!
그 말 하려고 얼마나 벼른 거야?
20분
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
무슨 일이 벌어졌는지 모르쇼?
사람이 죽어 가요!
컷!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
무슨 일이 벌어졌는지 모르쇼?
사람이 죽어 가요!
컷!
Cut!
Can't you see what's going on here?
This man is dying!
무슨 일이 벌어졌는지 모르쇼?
사람이 죽어 가요!
엄마!
Mommy!
무슨 일이 벌어졌는지 모르쇼?
사람이 죽었어요!
Can't you see what's going on?
This man is dead!